<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Christopher Joy | chrisjoy.asia on Christopher Joy</title>
    <link>http://www.chrisjoy.asia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Christopher Joy | chrisjoy.asia on Christopher Joy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="http://www.chrisjoy.asia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Christopher Joy | chrisjoy.asia</title>
      <link>http://www.chrisjoy.asia/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chrisjoy.asia/about/</guid>
      <description>About Christopher recently graduated with Distinction from SOAS, University of London with a Post-Graduate Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Area Studies (Southeast Asia). His research and interests focus on the politics, cultures and political economies of both mainland and island Southeast Asia. His thesis explored the early success of Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s COVID-19 response in the context of state-society relations. He also hold two Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degrees from the University of Pittsburgh.
He has worked predominately in the Asia-Pacific region.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christopher Joy | Contact</title>
      <link>http://www.chrisjoy.asia/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chrisjoy.asia/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact
Email: chrisjoy@fastmail.to
Phone: +1 Four One Two Four Four Eight Fourteen Thirty-Nine</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christopher Joy | CV</title>
      <link>http://www.chrisjoy.asia/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chrisjoy.asia/cv/</guid>
      <description>Email: chrisjoy@fastmail.to
Phone: +1 Four One Two Four Four Eight Fourteen Thirty-Nine
EDUCATION SOAS, University of London MA Area Studies (Southeast and Pacific Asian Studies) with Distinction, Dec. &amp;lsquo;22 Major/Thesis: Politics of Southeast Asia University of Pittsburgh B.Sc. Finance, cum laude B.Sc. Information Science, cum laude SKILLS AND STRENGTHS Research – Detail oriented research abilities with a willingness to perform exhaustive literature reviews and seek relevant interdisciplinary ideas Southeast &amp;amp; Pacific Asian) Flexible - Successful leader and subordinate capable of working with people of from a variety of backgrounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christopher Joy | CV</title>
      <link>http://www.chrisjoy.asia/cvold/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chrisjoy.asia/cvold/</guid>
      <description>Email: chrisjoy@fastmail.to
Phone: +1 Four One Two Four Four Eight Fourteen Thirty-Nine
Experienced former Tech Analyst with years of professional, consulting, operations and project management experience making a career change Experienced former Tech Analyst with years of professional, consulting, operations and project management experience making a career change
Decade-plus experience as a working professional including stints as a consultant and project manager Successfully led multiple teams through project inception to completion, and post-hoc support Successfully rose from intern to Senior Analyst, to starting my own development firm and eventually landed in freelance/consulting roles Degrees SOAS, University of London (2021 - 22) MA Area Studies, Southeast and Pacific Asian Studies, graduated with distinction, Nov.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christopher Joy | Works</title>
      <link>http://www.chrisjoy.asia/works/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chrisjoy.asia/works/</guid>
      <description>Selected Works BRIEF: World Superpowers, Sanctions and Semiconductors - 12/2022
Analysis of semiconductor market through lens of US/China trade conflict with special focus on Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s gains
The Embedded State and Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s COVID-19 Response (Awaiting Publication/Access) - 12/22 - SOAS, University of London, Postgraduate Master&amp;rsquo;s Dissertation/Thesis
From the paper&amp;rsquo;s abstract: &amp;ldquo;The COVID-19 pandemic illuminated both state failures and state successes with the pandemic itself being a sui generis event. Few countries saw more success than Vietnam, a country considered to have low or limited resources, through much of 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
